<!--

     Copyright 2018 Electric Cloud, Inc.

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

         http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.

-->
<editor>
    <formElement>
        <type>project</type>
        <label>Environment Project Name:</label>
        <property>envProjectName</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>The project containing the existing environment, or where the new environment will be created.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Environment Name:</label>
        <property>envName</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Provide the name of an existing environment that contains the OpenShift-backend cluster to be discovered. If the environment does not already exist, provide the OpenShift connection details below for discovery, and a new environment will be created.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Cluster Name:</label>
        <property>clusterName</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>In an existing environment, provide the name of the ElectricFlow cluster representing the OpenShift cluster whose deployed services are to be discovered. If the environment does not already exist, provide the name of the cluster to be created in the new environment.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <property>ecp_kubernetes_apiEndpoint</property>
        <label>OpenShift API Endpoint:</label>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The endpoint at which the OpenShift API will be reachable. Must be an IP address or a resolvable DNS name. This field is required and used only if you are not providing an existing environment above for discovery.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>textarea</type>
        <label>Service Account API Token:</label>
        <required>0</required>
        <property>ecp_kubernetes_apiToken</property>
        <documentation>Service account bearer token for a service account which has permissions to create resources in the OpenShift cluster. This field is required and used only if you are not providing an existing environment above for discovery.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>OpenShift project:</label>
        <property>namespace</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <value>default</value>
        <documentation>The name of the OpenShift project within which the deployed services should be discovered. Default to 'default' namespace.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>project</type>
        <label>Project Name:</label>
        <property>projName</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>The name of project in which the discovered microservices will be created.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <label>Create Microservices within an Application:</label>
        <checkedValue>true</checkedValue>
        <uncheckedValue>false</uncheckedValue>
        <required>0</required>
        <property>ecp_kubernetes_applicationScoped</property>
        <documentation>(Optional) Select to create all discovered services in the OpenShift project within one application in ElectricFlow. If selected, then the application name must be provided. If unselected, microservices will be created at the top-level in the project.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Application Name:</label>
        <required>0</required>
        <property>ecp_kubernetes_applicationName</property>
        <documentation>The name of the new application that will contain the microservices. Required only if 'Create Microservices within an Application' is selected.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
